("Should I Stay Or Should
I Go?" By The Clash)
♪ Darling you got to let me know ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go ♪
♪ If you say that you are mine ♪
♪ I'll be here 'till the end of time ♪
♪ So you got to let me know ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go ♪
♪ It's always tease tease tease ♪
♪ You're happy when I'm on my knees ♪
♪ One day it's fine and next it's black ♪
♪ So if you want me off your back ♪
♪ Well come on and let me know ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go now ♪
♪ If I go there will be trouble ♪
♪ And if I stay it will be double ♪
♪ So come on and let me know ♪
♪ This indecision's bugging me ♪
♪ Esta indecisión me molesta ♪
♪ If you don't want me set me free ♪
♪ Si no me quieres librarme ♪
♪ Exactly whom I'm supposed to be ♪
♪ Dígame que tengo ser ♪
♪ Don't you know which
clothes even fit me ♪
♪ Sabes que ropa me quedrá ♪
♪ Come on and let me know ♪
♪ Me tienes que decir ♪
♪ Should I cool it or should I blow ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go now ♪
♪ Yo me enfrío o lo soplo ♪
♪ If I go there will be trouble ♪
♪ Si me voy va a haber peligro ♪
♪ And if I stay it will be double ♪
♪ Si me quedo sera el doble ♪
♪ So ya gotta let me know ♪
♪ Me tienes que decir ♪
♪ Should I cool it or should I blow ♪
♪ Tengo frío por los ojos ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go now ♪
♪ If I go there will be trouble ♪
♪ Si me voy va haber peligro ♪
♪ And if I stay it will be double ♪
♪ Si me quedo será el doble ♪
♪ So ya gotta let me know ♪
♪ Me tienes que decir ♪
♪ Should I stay or should I go ♪